Finding Aid for francisco
Clarke Historical Library
- Francisco Photography Studio Photographic Collection is open for research.
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Loomis, Betty - 2.5-year-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 390)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Loomis, Buhl - Boy,undated (Box 5, Folder 391)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Loomis, Donald,undated (Box 5, Folder 392)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Loomis, Florence - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 393)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Loomis, Iva,July 7, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 394)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Loomis, R. - 1.5 -year-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 395)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Loomis, Virgil,August 2, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 396)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Loomis, W.R.,undated (Box 5, Folder 397)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lorency, Donald - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 398)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lorency, Rose Marie,undated (Box 5, Folder 399)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lorenz, Mary Lou,undated (Box 5, Folder 400)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lorenz, Pete,undated (Box 5, Folder 401)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Losey, Paul,undated (Box 5, Folder 402)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Losey, Shirley,undated (Box 5, Folder 403)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Louch, Beverly,undated (Box 5, Folder 404)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lough, Gene,undated (Box 5, Folder 405)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lough, Richard - Baby Girl,undated (Box 5, Folder 406)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Love, Bessie,undated (Box 5, Folder 407)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lovejoy, Pat,undated (Box 5, Folder 408)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lowe, Nick,undated (Box 5, Folder 409)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lowther, Ed and Wife,January 8, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 410)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lowther, Pat,undated (Box 5, Folder 411)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Luce, Cliff,August 30, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 412)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Ludtke, Ted,March 3, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 413)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Ludwig, Chas. - Copy,December 1961 (Box 5, Folder 414)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Ludwig, Evelyn,undated (Box 5, Folder 415)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Ludwig, Phyllis,undated (Box 5, Folder 416)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lueder, Irvin,undated (Box 5, Folder 417)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lueder, Otis and Wife,April 30, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 418)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lueder, Paul,undated (Box 5, Folder 419)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lumbert, A. - Baby,undated (Box 5, Folder 420)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lynch, Raymond,undated (Box 5, Folder 421)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lyon, Sandra,undated (Box 5, Folder 422)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lyons, Francis,undated (Box 5, Folder 423)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Lyou, Udele,undated (Box 5, Folder 424)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, MacArthur, Robert Franklin,undated (Box 5, Folder 425)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, MacDonald, Bob,undated (Box 5, Folder 426)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, MacGregor, Donald,undated (Box 5, Folder 427)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Machuta, Frank,undated (Box 5, Folder 428)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Machuta, Hope,undated (Box 5, Folder 429)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Machuta, John - Girl,undated (Box 5, Folder 430)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Machuta, Regina,undated (Box 5, Folder 431)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, MacInoy, Ruth,undated (Box 5, Folder 432)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mahaffey, Evelyn,undated (Box 5, Folder 433)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mahaffey, Helen,undated (Box 5, Folder 434)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mahaffey, Joe and Wife,undated (Box 5, Folder 435)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mahon, Chas. - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 436)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mallay, Chas.,undated (Box 5, Folder 437)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mallay, Nathan,undated (Box 5, Folder 438)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Maltby, Rozella,undated (Box 5, Folder 439)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Manausa, Thomas - Boy,undated (Box 5, Folder 440)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mardiny, Benny,undated (Box 5, Folder 441)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Margenstern, Larry - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 442)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Marino, Mallony,undated (Box 5, Folder 443)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Markham, M.,December 20, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 444)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Marks, Betty,undated (Box 5, Folder 445)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Marks, Florence,undated (Box 5, Folder 446)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Marks, George,undated (Box 5, Folder 447)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Marks, Hrisovla, Mrs.,June 24, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 448)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Marks, Ike,undated (Box 5, Folder 449)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Marquardt, Dick,undated (Box 5, Folder 450)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mars, Jack,undated (Box 5, Folder 451)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Marsh, M. G., Mrs.,October 13, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 452)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Martin, Harry,undated (Box 5, Folder 453)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Martin, K.P., Mrs.,undated (Box 5, Folder 454)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Martin, Leon,undated (Box 5, Folder 455)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Martin, Marvin - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 456)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Martin, Nancy,undated (Box 5, Folder 457)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Martin, Wilford - Copy,July 16, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 458)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Martinez, Dorothy,undated (Box 5, Folder 459)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mashagama Trip with a Man,undated (Box 5, Folder 460)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Masonic Lodge - Copy -Ed Bailey,undated (Box 5, Folder 461)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Massey, Royal,undated (Box 5, Folder 462)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mathews, Dave and Girlfriend,undated (Box 5, Folder 463)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Matts, G.,October 21, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 464)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Maxon, [no first name] - Boy,undated (Box 5, Folder 465)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Maxon, Dorothy,undated (Box 5, Folder 466)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Maxwell, William,undated (Box 5, Folder 467)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Maybee, Dale,undated (Box 5, Folder 468)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Maybee, Milan,undated (Box 5, Folder 469)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mayville, Anne,1950 (Box 5, Folder 470)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mayville, E. Arvne,undated (Box 5, Folder 471)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McBride, Eugene (Junney),undated (Box 5, Folder 472)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McBride, Nelson -4-month-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 473)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McBride, Rachel,December 2, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 474)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McBride, Rutt (Rutney),undated (Box 5, Folder 475)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McCabe, Jim - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 476)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McCarthy, [no first name],undated (Box 5, Folder 477)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McCarthy, Janice,undated (Box 5, Folder 478)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McCaul, Gerald - 1-year-old Boy,undated (Box 5, Folder 479)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McClintic, Gary,undated (Box 5, Folder 480)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McClintic, Shirley,undated (Box 5, Folder 481)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McConnell, Chas. - Daughter's Wedding,undated (Box 5, Folder 482)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McConnell, Jesse,undated (Box 5, Folder 483)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McConnell, Matt,undated (Box 5, Folder 484)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McConnell, Nikki,July 24, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 485)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McCord, Gerald - 8- and 12-year-olds,undated (Box 5, Folder 486)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McCord, Jerry -2 Children,undated (Box 5, Folder 487)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McCrimmon, Betty,undated (Box 5, Folder 488)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McCullough, Ron,undated (Box 5, Folder 489)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, [no first name],undated (Box 5, Folder 490)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, Barbara - 2-year-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 491)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, Barbara - 2 Children - 2- and 8-year-olds,undated (Box 5, Folder 492)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, Chas.,April 7, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 493)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, Ed - 7-month-old,September 1961 (Box 5, Folder 494)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, Elton -18-month-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 495)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, Elwood, and Mrs.,undated (Box 5, Folder 496)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, Fred - Family, Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 497)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, Gerald -7-month-old (2),September 20, 1966; December 12, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 498)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, John - 8-month-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 499)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, Kay - 7-month-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 500)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDonald, Mike,September 28, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 501)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McDowell, M.K., Mrs. (3),June 25, 1963; June 12, 1965; August 24, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 502)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McIntosh, Ed - 2 Children,undated (Box 5, Folder 503)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McKenzie, John,undated (Box 5, Folder 504)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McKinnon, Archie,undated (Box 5, Folder 505)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McLachlin, Betty,undated (Box 5, Folder 506)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McLacklin, Dolores,undated (Box 5, Folder 507)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McLacklin, Maxine,undated (Box 5, Folder 508)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McNamara, Raymond - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 509)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McNeal, Al,August 30, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 510)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McNeal, Francis,July 7, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 511)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McNeal, Lisa,March 25, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 512)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McNeil, W.,undated (Box 5, Folder 513)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McNeilley, R.,undated (Box 5, Folder 514)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McNerney, Chas.,undated (Box 5, Folder 515)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McPhail, John,undated (Box 5, Folder 516)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McQuaid, Sue,undated (Box 5, Folder 517)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McQueen, Carl,undated (Box 5, Folder 518)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McQueen, Dick,undated (Box 5, Folder 519)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McQueen, Lee - Daughter and Child,undated (Box 5, Folder 520)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McQueen, Richard - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 521)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McQueen, Roy,undated (Box 5, Folder 522)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McQuirk, Gerry, Mrs. - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 523)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McTaggert, Pat, Mrs.,undated (Box 5, Folder 524)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, McWilliams, Karin,undated (Box 5, Folder 525)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Meade, James,1957 (Box 5, Folder 526)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Meade, Jim -2 Children,undated (Box 5, Folder 527)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Meade, R.,undated (Box 5, Folder 528)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Meade, Randall,undated (Box 5, Folder 529)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Meffert, Laura - 2- and 3-year-olds,undated (Box 5, Folder 530)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Meister, E.J.,undated (Box 5, Folder 531)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Meller, Ernest, Mrs.,undated (Box 5, Folder 532)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Merrifield, Barbara,undated (Box 5, Folder 533)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Merrihew, Theron,undated (Box 5, Folder 534)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Merrill, Dorothy,undated (Box 5, Folder 535)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Merritt, Gene - 11-month-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 536)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Meyer, Angel,undated (Box 5, Folder 537)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Michigan Child Guidance Clinic,undated (Box 5, Folder 538)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Miller, A.E.,undated (Box 5, Folder 539)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Miller, Carol,undated (Box 5, Folder 540)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Miller, Geneve - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 541)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Miller, Jack,undated (Box 5, Folder 542)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Miller, Jerry - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 543)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Miller, Larry,undated (Box 5, Folder 544)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Miller, Lona,undated (Box 5, Folder 545)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Milligan, Don,1954 (Box 5, Folder 546)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Milligan, Don and Julia, Mrs. - 1st Communion,undated (Box 5, Folder 547)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Milligan, Geo.,undated (Box 5, Folder 548)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Milligan, Marianne, [original]; Resitting (2),September 14, 1968; May 3, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 549)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mills, Agnes,undated (Box 5, Folder 550)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mills, Mary,undated (Box 5, Folder 551)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Minics, James and Walt,January 18, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 552)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Missersmith, Russell - 3 Children,undated (Box 5, Folder 553)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mississagua River, Ontario, Canada,undated (Box 5, Folder 554)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mitchell, Ron,undated (Box 5, Folder 555)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moe, Edwin,undated (Box 5, Folder 556)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moeggenberg, Harry and Wife,December 5, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 557)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moerlins, Mike,undated (Box 5, Folder 558)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mogg, Pete,undated (Box 5, Folder 559)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mogg, Reynold - 5-month-old Girl,undated (Box 5, Folder 560)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moody, Gorden, Mrs. - Third grade,undated (Box 5, Folder 561)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moore, Chester, Mrs.,undated (Box 5, Folder 562)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moore, H.E.,undated (Box 5, Folder 563)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moore, John - Copy,July 3, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 564)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moore, Lena E.,July 7, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 565)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moore, Pat - Wedding,undated (Box 5, Folder 566)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moore, Robt. - Wedding,undated (Box 5, Folder 567)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moore, Ruth,July 7, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 568)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moorehead, Wm. - 2-year-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 569)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moorre, Lyle - Boy,undated (Box 5, Folder 570)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moose, Nan,undated (Box 5, Folder 571)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moran, Connie,May 8, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 572)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moran, Tony, Mrs. - 2 Children,undated (Box 5, Folder 573)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Morey, Connie,undated (Box 5, Folder 574)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Morfort, [no first name],undated (Box 5, Folder 575)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Morgan, Jerry,undated (Box 5, Folder 576)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Morrison, Murrey,undated (Box 5, Folder 577)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Morse, Chester - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 578)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mosher, Bob,undated (Box 5, Folder 579)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mosher, Gene,undated (Box 5, Folder 580)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mosher, Norris, Jr.,undated (Box 5, Folder 581)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Moss, Genna,undated (Box 5, Folder 582)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mrazek, J. - 2 Children,undated (Box 5, Folder 583)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mueller, James,undated (Box 5, Folder 584)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mull, [no first name] (2 envelopes),January 24, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 585)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mullet, Wm., Jr.,undated (Box 5, Folder 586)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mullikin, Velma,undated (Box 5, Folder 587)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mumy, Joyce,undated (Box 5, Folder 588)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Mumy, Pauline,undated (Box 5, Folder 589)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Munn, Edna - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 590)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Munn, Geo. and Wife,undated (Box 5, Folder 591)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Muny, Frank and Wife,undated (Box 5, Folder 592)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Murphy, John,undated (Box 5, Folder 593)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Murphy, Kay,undated (Box 5, Folder 594)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Murphy, Mary S.undated (Box 5, Folder 595)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Murphy, Leo, Mrs.,undated (Box 5, Folder 596)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Murphy, Mike,July 15, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 597)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Murphy, Mike,undated (Box 5, Folder 598)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Murphy, Pat,undated (Box 5, Folder 599)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Murphy, Sheila,undated (Box 5, Folder 600)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Murphy, William F.,undated (Box 5, Folder 601)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Myers, Eleanor,undated (Box 5, Folder 602)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Myers, Franch - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 603)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Myers, Kenneth,undated (Box 5, Folder 604)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Myshack, Adam,undated (Box 5, Folder 605)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nagy, Mike - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 606)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nagy, Rhea,undated (Box 5, Folder 607)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nall, Mrs. - Copy 2,undated (Box 5, Folder 608)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Names, Chas., Mrs.,undated (Box 5, Folder 609)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nasku, Sharon,undated (Box 5, Folder 610)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Naslund, Ruth,undated (Box 5, Folder 611)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Naumes, Mike, Mrs. - Tommy,undated (Box 5, Folder 612)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Neale, Lorraine,undated (Box 5, Folder 613)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Neff, Dinah,undated (Box 5, Folder 614)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Neff, Jack,September 19, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 615)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Neff, Joyce,undated (Box 5, Folder 616)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Neff, Sherman,undated (Box 5, Folder 617)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nelson, Lonira,undated (Box 5, Folder 618)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nestle, Geo.,undated (Box 5, Folder 619)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nestle, Robert and Wife,undated (Box 5, Folder 620)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Newton, Cassie,undated (Box 5, Folder 621)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Neyer, Bob,undated (Box 5, Folder 622)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Neyer, F.M.,October 4, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 623)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Neyer, Mary A.,October 4, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 624)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Neyome, Fred,May 2, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 625)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Neyome, Jennie,undated (Box 5, Folder 626)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nicholson, Gretchen,July 7, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 627)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nick,undated (Box 5, Folder 628)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nickle, Mary Anne - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 629)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nickle, Martha - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 630)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nicks, E.A.,undated (Box 5, Folder 631)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nicks, Guy - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 632)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nicks, Helen,undated (Box 5, Folder 633)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nigl, Peg,undated (Box 5, Folder 634)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Niswonger, Stella - Air Force Sergeant,undated (Box 5, Folder 635)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nogy, Alex and Wife,undated (Box 5, Folder 636)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nolan, Joan,undated (Box 5, Folder 637)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Nontelle, Don,undated (Box 5, Folder 638)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Norain, V.A.,undated (Box 5, Folder 639)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Norther, Marie,undated (Box 5, Folder 640)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, O'Brien, Theresa,undated (Box 5, Folder 641)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, O'Conner, Bonnie - 10-month-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 642)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, O'Dell, [no first name] - Baby Girl,undated (Box 5, Folder 643)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, O'Dell, Pat - 9-month-old Boy,1961 (Box 5, Folder 644)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Offhill, Alice,undated (Box 5, Folder 645)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Offill, Nina,undated (Box 5, Folder 646)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, O'Green, P.W.,undated (Box 5, Folder 647)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Ohms, Donna,undated (Box 5, Folder 648)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, O'Neal, Pat,undated (Box 5, Folder 649)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Onstatt, Kenneth,undated (Box 5, Folder 650)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Onstatt, Sandra,undated (Box 5, Folder 651)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Opdycke, Diann,undated (Box 5, Folder 652)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Oplinger, Earl,undated (Box 5, Folder 653)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Oplinger, Earl - 1st Communion Boy,undated (Box 5, Folder 654)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Osborn, [no first name],undated (Box 5, Folder 655)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Ososki, Ed,undated (Box 5, Folder 656)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Overla, Mrs.,July 22, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 657)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Owen, Chas. - Family,undated (Box 5, Folder 658)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Paisley, Don - 3-year-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 659)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Palmer, Jerry,undated (Box 5, Folder 660)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Pantenburg, Carol,undated (Box 5, Folder 661)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Pappas, Myrtle,undated (Box 5, Folder 662)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Parker, E.W. - Baby,undated (Box 5, Folder 663)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Parker, George and Wife,undated (Box 5, Folder 664)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Parker, Rodney,November 15, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 665)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Parker, Roy,March 22, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 666)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Parks, Dick,undated (Box 5, Folder 667)